脏弹不在卡车里
The bomb was not in the truck.
不  长官  不在里面
No, sir. That's negative.
脏弹不在卡车里面
The bomb was not in the truck.
辐射小组正在检测
We have rad crews on the ground now.
是的  长官  我会与你保持联系
Yes, sir. I'll keep you apprised.
将搜查范围扩至三个街区
Keep the perimeter at a 3-block radius.
让那些媒体滚远点
And keep the press the hell outta here.
我们不能引起恐慌
We don't need a panic on our hands, all right?
长官  辐射小组已经完成了
Sir, radiation teams have finished sweeping
附近地区的扫描  没有脏弹存在的痕迹
the immediate area-- negative across the board.
如果他们移动了炸弹  一定不再附近
If they moved the device, it's not nearby.
没道理啊
It makes no sense.
-他们为什么要移走  -它是牛仔小丑
- Why would they move it? - It's a rodeo clown.
-牛仔小丑吗  -卡车只是为了虚晃一枪
- Rodeo clown? - The truck...it's a diversion.
杰马尔一定感觉到我们逼近了
Jamal must have sensed we were closing in.
他给我们一个诱饵  让我们远离真正的目标
He gave us something to chase, throw us off the target.
-他在耍我们  -也就是说我们又回到起点了
- He's playing us. - So we're back to square one?
我们得找到杰马尔  在他们的雇员上多下功夫
We gotta find Jamal. Move in on his employees.
调查整个公司
Shake the trees.
肯定有人知道内幕
Somebody's gotta know something.
你觉得法伦知不知道自己在追查的是个死人
You think Fallon knows he's chasing a dead man?
不知道  他只有在我们出去之后才会知道
No. And he won't know unless we get out of here.
你觉得他们会回来吗
Think they're coming back?
他们干嘛要回来
Why would they?
为了杰马尔
For Jamal.
不然他们干嘛把他的尸体放在冰柜里
Why else would they keep his body on ice?
这件事的主谋
Whoever's behind this
因为某种原因才把杰马尔的尸体冷藏起来
wanted to preserve his body for some reason.
我是这样想的
I'm thinking...
他们想把尸体和脏弹一起放到面包车里
they wanted his body in that van with the bomb.
那样的话  当脏弹爆炸的时候
That way, when the bomb goes off...
会使得他的尸首和DNA留在案发现场
They'd have his remains and his D.N.A. at the crime scene.
-人们就会认为他是恐怖分子  -没错
- People would think that he was the terrorist. - Right.
然后真正的恐怖分子就会逍遥法外
And then the real terrorists would get away scot-free.
好了  那现在的问题是  为什么
Okay, so then the question is, why?
他们到底打的什么如意算盘
What is their agenda?
我们俩待在这里面是不会查出来的
We're not gonna find out in here.
卡塞尔  明摆的事还用你说
Well, Castle, thank you for stating the obvious.
-你有信号吗  -没有
- You got anything? - No, no.
没有恒温器  也没有控制箱
No thermostat, no control box.
肯定是安在冰柜外面了
Must be on the outside.
你手机有信号吗
Got any bars on your phone?
没有
No.
等下  等下
Wait, wait, wait.
没有  你呢
No. You?
没有
No.
你觉得这里能有多冷
How cold do you think it is in here?
从感觉上来判断
Um, judging by the way that it feels,
我敢说绝对远低于零度
I'd say it's well below freezing.
你觉得咱俩穿成这样能撑多久
How long do you think we're gonna last dressed like this?
顶多几个小时
A couple of hours at the most.
我也这么觉得
That's what I thought, too.
那扇门是铁做的  我不认为
That door is made of steel. I don't...
我不认为你那样撞门能管用
I don't think that's gonna do anything.
卡塞尔  没人知道咱俩在这里
Castle, nobody knows that we're in here.
甚至没人会试图来找咱俩
Nobody even knows to look for us.
如果我们出不去就只能在这里冻死了
We're gonna freeze to death if we don't get outta here.
也许有别的方法可以出去
Well, maybe there's another way out.
好吧  倒数三下
Right. Uh... On three?
好  一  二
Yeah. One. Two.
-三  好  再来一次  一  -二
- Three. Okay, again. One. - Two.
三
Three.
再来  一
again. One.
-二  -三
- Two. - Three.
我们没有必要回来
We didn't have to come back.
-我挺好的  -挺好的吗
- I was fine, you know. - Fine?
我明显地感受到  我们离城越远
I could literally feel your anxiety level rising
你的焦躁程度就越发飙升
the further we got from the city.
一个灵修度假村
A spiritual retreat
应该让人放松身心  亲爱的
is supposed to be spiritual, darling,
不是充满压力
Not stressful.
等你没有考试缠身的时候
We'll do it another time when you don't have a test
我们再去吧
hanging over you.
尽管我能说出一大堆完美的借口
Although I could've written you a brilliant excuse.
我曾经在你爸身上用了很多经典的
I used to write the best ones for your father...
马戏团事故啊  公寓失火啊
Circus accidents, apartment...fires.
电影之夜吗
Movie night?
我不知道
I don't know.
他用了投影仪  但是
He has the projector up, but...
他不在家
he's not here.
也许他出去了  我的意思是...
Well, maybe he's out, as in...
明白  恶心  但他若是在外面肯定会打来电话
Yes. Ew. But he always calls when he's out
或是留下字条
or leaves a note.
他一想咱俩已经出城了
Well, he figured we were gone,
干嘛还要这么麻烦呢
so why bother?
很晚了  亲爱的  睡吧
It's late, darling. Come on.
我们明早上再问他
We'll ask him in the morning.
卡塞尔  这可不是好现象
Castle, that's not good.
的确不是
No, it's not.
好吧
All right.
往后站
Stand back. Mm.
-你要干嘛  -往后站就是了
- What are you gonna do? - Just stand back.
你想让咱俩早点挂掉吗
Are you trying to kill us sooner?
你难道有更好的办法吗
Do you have a better idea?
也许应该省几发子弹以防他们回来
Maybe just save a few rounds in case they come back.
卡塞尔
Castle...
在这困境中  我想找到
I could use a silver lining
最后一线生机  知道吗
right about now, okay?
知道
Yeah. Um...
我倒希望能有一线生机
I wish I had one.
这解释不通啊
This doesn't make any sense.
咋了  老兄
What, bro?
给杰马尔搬家公司打工的那帮家伙
These guys that work for Jamal's moving company,
他们的确是中东人
they are middle eastern,
但绝大多数已经成为了美国公民
but most of 'em are citizens
就出生在美国
born here in the states.
除了几次交通违章
Aside from a couple of traffic violations,
他们案底清白
their records are clean.
也许正因为这他们才被招募的
Maybe that's why they were recruited.
你现在说话的口气开始像法伦了
Now you're starting to sound like Fallon.
也许卡塞尔是对的
You know, maybe Castle was right.
也许这件案子的确是另有蹊跷
Maybe there is something else going on here.
莱恩
Ryan.
你查到什么了吗
You get anything?
到目前为止还没有
Nothing so far.
他们声称根本不知道杰马尔的行踪
They claim to not know anything about Jamal's whereabouts
也不知道他要干什么
or his activities.
那些请了律师的人
And the ones that are lawyering up
控诉我们歧视性种族评判
are accusing us of racial profiling.
他们没做错什么
They're not wrong.
你还好吧
You okay?
和核弹相比
Compared to a nuke,
脏弹是一种粗制的装置
a dirty bomb is a fairly crude device.
它被设计用来在居民区引起恐慌
It's designed to instill fear in the populace.
瞬间性的杀伤力将会主要
The majority of the immediate damage
来自传统式的爆炸物
is gonna come from the conventional explosion,
形成一个死亡区域
creating a kill zone.
就像俄克拉荷马市那次
Like Oklahoma city.
只不过这次不只会倒塌一栋大楼
Except for it's not just a building that falls.
它会辐射到好几个街区
It spreads radiation for several blocks.
那是次生死亡区域
That's your secondary kill zone.
如果没有及时治疗  人们会在不到一周内
If left untreated, people can die from radiation poisoning
因辐射中毒而死
in less than a week.
但是真正使其成为如此有效的恐怖袭击武器
But what makes this such an effective terror weapon
是其对外区域的影响
is the outer zone.
在这片区域  每个人一开始都没有不良反应
Now in this area, everybody seems fine at first.
随后开始有人患癌症
Then the cancers start showing up...
婴儿  小孩  成年人
babies, kids, adults.
每报告新增一起病例
And with every new case that's reported,
人们就涌进急诊室  让医疗系统几近崩溃
people flock to the emergency rooms, overwhelm the system.
就好像我们又被恐怖袭击了一样
It's like we're being attacked all over again.
如果我们找不到脏弹
Look, if we can't find the bomb,
也许我们可以找到袭击目标
maybe we can find the target.
动用手下所有人
Pull everybody you got.
给我一份接下来四十八小时内
Give me a list of every significant event
市内即将发生的所有重大事件的清单
going on in the city for the next 48 hours...
任何人口可能会密集的地方
anyplace were people might gather in large numbers.
这可是纽约  每天都有数以百计的
This is New York city. There are a hundred events
大事件发生  我们必须缩小范围
going on every day. We have to narrow it down.
集中关注政治性的或是涉及到政府的事件
Focus on anything political or government related.
这里要举办体育赛事吗
Are there any sporting events going on?
联合国总部最近有什么动静
What's happening at the U.N.?
他们选择现在袭击也许是有原因的
Maybe there's a reason they're choosing to strike now.
长官  我能和你单独谈谈吗
Sir, can I speak with you alone?
失陪
Excuse us.
什么事
So what's wrong?
我刚和卡塞尔的女儿通完电话
I just got off the phone with Castle's daughter.
显然他没有回家
Apparently, he hasn't come home,
而她至今无法接通她老爸的电话
and she hasn't been able to reach him on his cell.
-那又怎样  -卡塞尔被踢出特别行动组
- So? - Castle got kicked off the task force.
那他怎么可能不在家呢
Why isn't he at home?
我怎么知道
How should I know?
贝克特也一直没有接电话
Well, Beckett's not answering her phone either.
鉴于他俩的作风  我们想...
We thought, given their history, that...
我们认为他们可能卷入了某些事里
we thought the two of them might have got on to something.
你俩明白一个恐怖组织
You two do realize that a terrorist cell
正威胁袭击本市
is threatening to strike
无数生命危在旦夕吗
and thousands of lives may be at risk?
-明白  但是...  -你们想我怎么做
- Yes, sir. But-- - What do you want me to do,
派出一队搜索队
send out a search party
就因为你们的同伴半夜三更
because your pals aren't answering their cell phones
没接电话吗
in the middle of the night?
-他俩可能正在外头小酌呢  -头儿
- For all I know, they could be out having a cold one. - Captain--
感谢你们的担心
I appreciate your concern,
想必他们也跟我一样
and I'm sure they appreciate your concern,
但他们能照顾好自己
but they can take care of themselves.
况且  我们还要找一名恐怖分子
Besides, we have a terrorist to find.
遵命  头儿
Yes, sir.
卡塞尔
Castle.
你在吗
Are you there?
在在  我就在...
Yeah, yeah. No, I'm-- I'm right--
我就在这
I'm right here.
我都冻僵了
I can't feel anything.
我以前总是想....
I always thought...
当警察  最后准会中枪牺牲
being a cop, I'd take a bullet.
却从没想过会冻死
I never thought I'd freeze to death.
我们还没死啊
W-w-we're not dead yet.
我真希望这只是你的一个故事
I just wish this was one of your books.
那你就可以重写结局
Then you could rewrite the ending.
对
Mm.
我...对不起
I'm s--I'm sorry.
为什么道歉
For what?
都怪我太自我
Fo-for being me...
我行我素  结果把你拖进...
going rogue, getting you into...
这险境
into this.
如果我们没有单独行动
If we hadn't gone on our own--
嘘  别说了  卡塞尔
Oh, shh. Shh. Castle, no.
好吧  不说了
Okay? Shh. Shh.
你是对的
You were right.
我们找到了炸弹
We found the bomb.
但为时已晚了  好吧
We were just too late. Okay?
卡塞尔
Castle.
在
Yeah.
谢谢你陪着我
Thank you for being there.
我一直都在
Always.
我只是想告诉你我是多么...
I just want you to know how much I...
喂  凯特
Hey, Kate.
别睡  撑着
Stay with me.
凯特
Kate?
乖  乖
Shh. Shh.
别离开我
Stay with me.
翻译：Cam小池  咖啡十三  小易  落末一地  大卫熊
时间轴：小穗   校对：大卫熊   后期&总监：瓜瓜
冷静点  伙计
Easy, pal.
贝克特  她在哪里
Beckett. Where is she?
-先生  请你冷静下来  -她在哪里
- Sir, I'm gonna need you to calm down. - Where is she?
她没事  你俩都没事
She's gonna be fine. You're both fine.
-我们及时找到了你们  -乔什
- Got to you just in time. - Josh?
你刚从中度低温症恢复过来
Hey. So you're recovering from a moderate case of hypothermia.
短时间内你的行动会有点迟缓
And you're gonna be a little bit sluggish for a while,
但输完液  身子暖些后
But with some warmth and some fluids,
-就没问题了  -那个...我以为你去了海地
- you should be all right. - What... I thought you were in haiti.
没走成  这会有点疼
Mm-hmm. Didn't go. This is gonna hurt.
好了
Okay.
看看能不能扶你坐起来
Let's see if we can't get you to sit up.
好了  慢点儿
All right? Move slow.
行了
There you go.
我被救出来多久了
How long was I out?
-不清楚  大概一小时了吧  -炸弹
- Uh, I don't know. About an hour? - The bomb.
我们搜查了整座仓库  炸弹不见了
We searched the entire warehouse. It's gone.
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
阿丽克西斯打来  说你没回家
Oh, Alexis called. Said you didn't come home.
阿丽克西斯  她不是出城了吗
Alexis? She's supposed to be out of town.
我想她回来了
I guess she came back.
我们本以为你和贝克特在一块  直到乔什来电话
We figured you were with Beckett until Josh called.
我们想你们俩肯定在外头
We thought you must be out there
做着一些违反命令的大蠢事
doing something incredibly stupid against orders,
所以我们派出巡警
So we sent patrol units
四处巡查你俩笨得会单枪匹马前往的地方
everywhere we figured you'd be moronic enough to go.
接着找到了贝克特的车  搜查整个区域
Found Beckett's car, searched the area
最后找到了透着光线的贮藏箱
till we found the light from the storage container.
我很庆幸你们猜到我会做蠢事
Well, I'm glad my stupidity is predictable.
你们把我们救出来的吗
You pulled us outta there?
感激不尽
Thanks.
你的男朋友回来了
So your boy's back in town.
对
Mm-hmm.
他回来了
He came back.
那对你来说意味着什么
So what does that mean to you?
我和他还有希望
It means we have a chance.
来吧  法伦要听取汇报
Come on. Fallon wants to debrief.
你觉得他愿意相信咱们了吗
Think he's ready to believe us?
核能应急支持小组检测到了军用可变塑胶炸药
N.E.S.T. confirms high levels of residual radiation
和高强度残余辐射的痕迹
along with a military-grade semtex.
爆炸装置之前肯定放在了这里
There's no question that device was here.
我已派人调出此地
I'll have my team pull surveillance tape
四百米内的所有监控器的录像带
on every camera within a quarter-mile of here.
很好  我之后再向你跟进
Sounds good. I'll catch up to you.
-贝克特  -头儿
- Beckett. - Sir.
你们两个总是这么固执兼违抗命令的吗
You two. Are you always this stubborn and insubordinate?
只有当我们想拯救世人的时候会这样
Only when we're trying to save the world.
如果你们成功了  我会更赏识
I'd be more impressed if you succeeded.
你俩怎么知道找来这里的
How did you know to come here?
因为阿米尔的士上的监控器
Security cameras in Amir's cab.
我们认为他在监视租他车的
We think that he was keeping tabs on
其中一个司机凯文·麦凯恩
one of his drivers--Kevin Mccann.
我们调出了麦凯恩的行车记录
We pulled Mccann's route records.
结果发现他去过华盛顿高地
Turns out he visited that storage facility in Washington heights
存放着放射性物质的储藏公司
where the radioactive material was being kept
还早在阿米尔之前就来过这仓库
and this warehouse long before Amir did.
麦凯恩在他之前来过这里
Mccann was here before him?
对  看来阿米尔在跟踪麦凯恩
Yeah, it looks like Amir was following Mccann,
想查出他在密谋什么
trying to figure out what he was up to
结果自己却被抓住杀害了
until he was caught and killed.
因为他们原本的替罪羊阿米尔死了
And with Amir, their intended patsy dead,
我们认为他们想把
we think they were trying to
罪名栽赃给他的表哥杰马尔
implicate his cousin Jamal as the bomber.
所以他们才把他的尸体冷冻起来
That's why they were keeping his body on ice.
你们有看清在场的任何一名恐怖分子吗
Did you see any other members of the cell here?
没有  环境太暗了
No, it was dark.
-他们还开枪了  -但我们
- And they were shooting. - But we do
确定炸弹安放在一辆车后车侧
know that the bomb is housed in a white commercial van
都有车门的白色面包车里
with a rear and side passenger door.
在纽约找一辆白色面包车吗
A white van in new york city?
这个范围还真是"窄"啊
Well, that narrows it down.
我们看到了计时器  炸弹设置在今天4点爆炸
We saw the counter. It's set to go off at 4:00 today.
距离爆炸时间不足10小时了  好了
That's less than ten hours from now. All right.
我会设立关卡  但炸弹已经运到市里了
I'll put up checkpoints. But it's already in the city.
我知道所有的证据都指向阿米尔和杰马尔
Look, I know all the evidence points to Amir and Jamal,
但当中肯定有更重大的隐情
but something bigger is going on here,
凯文·麦凯恩绝对脱不了关系
and Kevin Mccann is involved.
收到  喂
Got it. Yo.
刚和的士公司联系过
That was a taxi company.
麦凯恩本该现在轮班
Mccann's supposed to be on shift right now,
但他却没有出现
but he didn't show up
他也没有接电话
and he's not answering his phone.
查到他家地址了吗
Did you get an address?
车管所登记的住址是
D.M.V. lists an apartment off
布朗克斯区杰若姆大道的一间公寓
Jerome Avenue in the Bronx.
好了  召集一个小队
All right. Get a team together.
-马上去那里抓人  -法伦探员
- Go up there and get him. - Agent Fallon?
-什么事  -鉴于目前情况  我们请求
- Yeah? - Given the circumstances, we'd like to request
重回特别行动组
to be reinstated on the task force.
那不是我说了算
Well, that's not up to me.
得由你的医生说了算  对吧
It'll be up to your doctor, isn't it?
真有趣
You know, it's funny.
我第一次见到你俩时  以为你俩是一对
When I first met you two, I thought you were together.
没有  我们只是朋友
Oh. No, just--just friends.
去洗个澡
Get cleaned up.
接下来  有我们忙的了
We got a long day ahead of us.
理查德  我的宝贝  你没事吧
Oh, Richard, darling. Oh, are you all right?
你还要披着那张毛毯吗
Are you using that blanket?
不用了  我正想给你
Oh, no. I'm gonna give it to you.
我可怜的儿子
Oh, you poor baby.
你看上去毫无生气
You look like death warmed over.
如果有人向你们推崇低温学说
If someone tries to sell you on cryogenics,
-别信他们  -我知道你不会不说一声
- say no. - I knew you wouldn't turn your phone off
就关掉手机的
without leaving me a message.
是因为那个的哥的命案吗
Now is this about the cab driver?
听着  我要你们为我做件事
Look, I need you girls to do something for me.
但我不希望你们多问
But I don't want you to ask any questions.
我要你们马上去汉普顿
I want you to go the Hamptons.
我要你们整个周末待在那里
I want you to stay there for the weekend.
理查德  究竟出什么事了
Richard, what is this about?
看  不让多问的
See, that-- that's a question.
听着  纽约可能会...
Look, there might be a...
有一场灾难....
an event...
继续留在市区  会有性命危险
that will make it very dangerous to stay in the city.
-你干什么  -打给阿什利
- What are you doing? - Calling Ashley.
不  不行  你不能告诉任何人
No, no, no, no. You can't tell anybody.
懂吗  不能告诉任何人  如果你告诉了阿什利
Okay? You can't tell anybody. You tell Ashley,
他一定会告诉他父母  他父母又会告诉亲朋好友
he'll tell his parents, they'll call someone they love,
那...就会造成市民恐慌
and...a panic will make this thing
让事件更加一发不可收拾
a thousand times harder to stop.
-爸  他是我男朋友  -我知道
- Dad, he's my boyfriend. - I know.
-这不公平  你不能...  -这跟公不公平无关
- This isn't fair. You can't-- - Fair has nothing to do with it.
我要你们马上动身
I need you to go. Now.
但你会来吗
But you'll come to?
可以的时候我会来
I will when I can.
但我需要你们离开
But I need you to go.
马上
Now.
好吧
Okay.
我想你需要咖啡因和这股热乎劲儿
Figured you could use the caffeine and the warmth.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
你有想过法伦吗
You ever wonder about Fallon?
对他说  那是怎样的感觉
I mean, what this must be like for him,
天天过着这样的生活
living this every day?
我让阿丽克西斯和我妈出城去
I told Alexis and my mother to get out of town.
我没告诉她们原因  但她们知道
I didn't tell them why, but they knew.
她们想告诉朋友
They wanted to tell their friends,
而我说不可以
and I told them they couldn't.
我觉得自己像个恶人
I felt like a monster.
我是说  如果这种感觉一直伴随着你
I mean, that must be some kind of hell...
肯定是很难熬的
feeling that all the time.
让想你知道
Kinda makes you wonder
自911之后  有多少这样的事发生
how many times this has happened since 9/11
而我们却蒙在鼓里
and we were the ones who didn't know.
麦凯恩的住址是个死胡同
Yeah, the Mccann address is a dead end.
一个韩国裔家庭住在这里
Korean family lives here.
已经住了4年
Been living here for the past four years.
你搜查过房子吗
Did you search the place?
是的  但没有发现异常
Yeah, didn't seem to be anything out of the ordinary.
但我们问了一个老邻居  他们说
But we did talk to a longtime neighbor, and they said
麦凯恩一家曾在这住过  已是十几年前了
the Mccann family lived here, but it was over a decade ago.
她记起他们有个儿子叫凯文
She seems to recall something about them having a son,
他参了军
named Kevin, and he went in the military.
凯文·麦凯恩
Kevin Mccann--
属特种部队  六次前往阿富汗服役
Army special forces, recipient of two purple hearts
授予两枚紫心勋章
and the distinguished service medal
和陆军杰出服务十字勋章
during his six tours in Afghanistan.
六次吗
Six tours?
现在越来越少人当兵了
Military is stretched pretty thin these days.
这说不通啊
Doesn't make any sense.
一位战争英雄怎么跟恐怖袭击搅在一起
What's a war hero doing mixed up in a terrorist plot?
别看我  这是你的推论
Don't look at me, pal. It's your theory.
他们有地址吗
Do they have an address listed?
阿林顿国家公墓  弗吉尼亚州
Arlington, Virginia.
凯文·麦凯恩
Kevin Mccann--
真正的凯文·麦凯恩
The real Kevin Mccann-- died a couple of years back
几年前在战场受重伤
at a V.A. Hospital from complications of wounds
死在了退伍军人医院
he suffered during combat ops.
以最高荣誉葬于阿林顿国家公墓
Buried at Arlington with full honors.
有人盗用了他的身份
So someone stole his identity.
可以是任何人
He could be anyone,
也可能是外国特务
including a foreign agent.
把这个和联邦调查局和中情局
Run this through FBI and CIA
甚至是国际刑警组织的脸部识别数据库作对比
facial recognition databases all the way up to interpol.
我要这家伙的一切资料
I want to know everything I can about this guy.
技术组追查到
All right, so tech tracked the phone
他化名为麦凯恩的电话
that he's been using under the Mccann name.
巡警刚在垃圾桶找到的  擦拭得很干净
Patrol units just found it in a dumpster. Been wiped clean.
我们发出了全面通缉令
We've got an A.P.B. out on him and
给每个人派发他的照片
we sent copies of his photo to everyone.
小分队正前往出租车库
Teams are on their way to the taxi depot
扣查他开过的车  套取指纹
and the impound to pull prints from the cabs he drove,
但有太多的司机和乘客
but with multiple drivers and passengers,
每一辆车上都有成百个指纹
there are gonna be hundreds of prints in each cab.
颇费时间
It's gonna take some time.
我们没有时间了
It's time we don't have.
他为何要偷麦凯恩的身份吗
Why would he steal Mccann's identity?
我原以为这家伙是犯罪小说家
I thought this guy was a crime novelist?
我是
I-I am.
那你就该知道有时犯了法的人
Then you should know that sometimes people who operate
会拿已故者的社保号
outside the law will take the social security number
用来伪造一个新身份
of a deceased individual and use it to forge a new identity.
我知道  我书里出现3次了
I know. I've done it three times in my books.
我想说的是
What I'm saying is,
为什么他要偷凯文·麦凯恩的身份
why would he steal Kevin Mccann's identity?
因为这很方便
Because it was convenient.
为什么方便呢
Why was it convenient?
为了诬陷阿米尔  打进他
I mean, the money that was deposited into Amir's account
账户上的钱
to implicate him,
我们追查到阿富汗
we tracked it back to Afghanistan.
麦凯恩曾在阿富汗服役
Mccann served in Afghanistan.
也许这其中有关联
Maybe there's a link.
怎样的关联
What kind of link?
我不知道  也许这家伙并不是
I don't know. Maybe... Maybe this guy wasn't just
随便偷一个死人的身份
Stealing the identity of some random dead guy.
也许  麦凯恩是他认识的人
Maybe... Mccann is someone he knew
或是他必须冒名顶替的人
or someone he needed to be.
联系国防部
Contact the pentagon.
-调查麦凯恩的一切  -收到
- Get everything you can on Mccann.  - On it.
他家人曾住在这里  他们还住这附近
His family used to live here. Are they still around?
父母已过世  但有个妹妹住在皇后区
Parents are dead, but he's got a sister in Queens.
抱歉这里乱糟糟的
Sorry about the mess.
道格离开后  生活很艰难
It's just--it's been hard since Doug left.
亲爱的  去你房里玩
Sweetie, just go play in your room.
发生什么事了
so what happened?
我那游手好闲的前夫又被抓了
My deadbeat ex got arrested again?
麦凯恩女士  其实是关于你哥哥的事
Actually, ms. Mccann, we're here about your brother.
是的  我认识他
Yeah, I know him.
拉福德
That's Radford.
拉福德·海耶斯
Radford Hayes.
跟我哥一个分队的  他们是挚友
He was in my brother's unit. They were best friends.
他假冒你哥哥的身份
He assumed your brother's identity.
你知道原因吗
Do you have any idea why?
不知道
No.
你有多了解他
How well did you know him?
主要从我哥哥的信中了解的
Mostly from my brother's letters.
他们都在退伍军人医院
They were in the V.A. together.
凯文死的时候  他陪在我身边
He was there with me when... When Kevin died.
他信中有表达
In his letters, did he ever display
对国家的仇恨吗
any animosity toward this country?
他为何问我这个
Why is he asking me that?
海耶斯先生有可能
There's a possibility that Mr. Hayes is working
与一群极端份子策划袭击美国
with a set of extremists who are plotting against the U.S.
不
No.
科琳
Colleen?
凯文死后  拉福德带我去喝酒
Radford took me out for a beer after Kevin died,
他当时愤愤不平
and he was angry--
气愤大家不再关心战争
Angry at how everyone stopped caring about the war.
好像这战争从未发生过
Like it wasn't even happening,
恼火政客对待士兵的方式
Angry at the way politicians were treating soldiers,
好像他们是纸巾  利用完就扔一边
like they were tissue paper, to be used and thrown away.
他觉得华盛顿那帮家伙
He thought the folks in Washington
更关心达到政治目标  而非胜利
cared more about scoring political points than winning.
他说也许这国家需要
He said that maybe what this country needed
敲响另一记警钟
was another wake-up call.
也许下一次  会达到目的
Maybe next time, we'd get it right.
你知道在哪可以找到他吗
Do you know where we can find him?
不知道
No.
我只有他的手机号
All I have is his cell phone number.
他手机开机了  但款式很旧  无自带GPS
His phone's active, but it's old-school. No native gps.
多久才能定位到他
How long before you get a fix on him?
我需要几分钟通过手机信号塔三角定位
I'll need a few minutes to triangulate off the cell towers.
放手去做  别让他知道我们在追踪他
Do what you gotta do. Just don't let him know we're coming.
很难相信我们在追踪自己人
I can't believe we're chasing one of our own.
他没有错  过去我们上战场
He's not wrong, you know? Used to be, we'd go to war,
大家牺牲和奉献
everybody sacrifices, everybody pitches in.
现在新闻上都看不到了
Now you don't even see it on the news.
我不是在为他辩护
I'm not defending him.
我只是说我理解他的愤慨
I'm just saying, I understand the anger.
阿米尔是完美的替罪羊
Well, Amir is the perfect patsy.
武器工程的背景  与叙利亚有关联
He has a background in weapons engineering, ties to Syria,
正是阿尔盖达组织招募的理想对象
which is a hotbed for Al Qaeda recruiting.
上面写满了恐怖主义
I mean, it has terrorist written all over it.
他阿富汗账户里的钱
And the money from his Afghanistan account
使人们相信塔利班参与其中
would've had people believing Taliban was involved.
恐惧让我们很程序化
We're so programmed by fear.
人们完全如拉福德所愿
People are gonna believe exactly what Radford wants us
相信我们又遭恐怖袭击了
to believe-that we were attacked again--
他们就会血战血偿
and then they're gonna cry out for blood.
还剩不到4个小时
Less than four hours.
如果不能阻止  我们不该公之于众吗
If we can't stop it, shouldn't we tell people?,
告诉大家什么  有个脏弹
Tell 'em what, That a dirty bomb
将在曼哈顿某个地方爆炸吗
is gonna go off somewhere in Manhattan?
知道那会引起怎样的恐慌吗
You know the kind of panic that would create?
不  我们唯一的希望就是阻止这事
No. Our only hope is to stop this thing.
希望我们可以
Let's just hope that we can.
找到他了  出发
We got him. Let's roll.
海耶斯
Hayes!
趴下  趴下
Get down! Get down!
-趴下  -趴下  马上
- Get down! - Get down! Now!
跪下  跪下
On your knees! On your knees!
双手放在脑后
Interlock your fingers behind your head!
好的
Yeah.
告诉我在哪里
Tell me where it is.
炸弹在哪里  在哪里
Where's the bomb? Where is it?
炸弹在哪里
Where's the bomb?
这家伙让我恶心
This guy makes me sick.
他曾发誓要保卫国家
He swore an oath to defend this country.
他觉得自己是爱国者
In his mind, he's a patriot.
就像蒂姆·麦克维
Yeah, like Tim Mcveigh.
莱恩  联系国防部
Ryan, contact D.O.D.
看能否找到
See if you can get 20s
跟这家伙在阿富汗服役的战友的情况
on the guys he served with in Afghanistan.
看有谁销声匿迹了
see if any of 'em are blowin' in the wind.
准备好没
You ready?
好了
Yeah.
不管怎样都得撬开他嘴
We break him, no matter what.
明白
Got it.
我知道你很生气
Look, I know you're angry,
我也很理解
and I understand.
但你所做的  你的计划
But what you're doing, what you're involved with
是不对的
it's not the way.
拉福德  你是一名士兵
Radford, you're a soldier.
这城市里的人们不是你的敌人
The people in this city are not your enemies.
我不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
听着  我们知道你
Look, we know about you
在华盛顿高地储藏室里的秘密
going up to the storage facilities in Washington heights
还有仓库的事
and the warehouse.
怎么了
What about it?
我们知道
Well, we know that there was
那个储藏室里有放射性物质
nuclear material in the storage facility.
炸弹在仓库组装
The bomb was assembled in the warehouse,
所以别当我们白痴  跟我们说你一无所知
so don't insult us and tell us you don't know anything about it.
-他在浪费时间  -为什么这么说
- He's wasting his time. - Why do you say that?
他是特种兵  受过专业训练
He's special forces. We're trained for this--
决不会泄漏半点消息
Never to give up information,
就算被捕  也决不放弃自己的立场
never to give up your position if you're captured.
他们没法说服他  来不及
They can't break him. Not in time.
你是不是当自己是
Do you see yourself as a
为了伟大事业而献身的英雄
a great hero doing this for a-a mighty cause?
你以为大家也会这么看你吗
You think that's how people are gonna see you?
因为我现在就告诉你  老兄
Because I'll tell you right now, brother,
你要是真做了这种事  你就会遗臭万年
if you let this happen, you're gonna go down in history
成为美国臭名昭著的屠杀者
as America's greatest mass murderer.
这就是你想要的吗
Is that what you want?
炸弹爆炸的时候
When this bomb goes off,
你以为他们会想到我吗
do you think they're gonna be looking at me?
人们会把这当做恐怖袭击
People will see this as an act of terrorism,
然后开始寻找恐怖分子
so they will be looking for a terrorist,
而不是爱国者  决不是自己人
not a patriot, not one of their own.
原来你自以为是爱国者
Is that what you think you are, a patriot?
有一个词专门用来形容你这种人
There's a word for people like you,
不过不是"爱国者"
And it's not "patriot."
而是"叛国者"
It's "traitor."
当局对叛国者来说没用
The powers that be have no use for a traitor.
等他们找到了恐怖分子
So when they find their terrorist,
当然他们一定会找到恐怖分子
and they will find their terrorist,
你觉得我会怎么样
what do you think will happen to me?
我来告诉你  因为我了解他们
Well, let me tell you, because I know them,
所以我知道他们的思维方式
I know how they think.
我会成为你一堆陈旧文件里
I will become a footnote in one of your files
一个小小注脚  永远都不会被注意
buried so far back, no one will ever find it,
因为任何多余的东西
because anything more would be an inconvenience
都会妨碍他们自私自利蛊惑民心的演说
to their self-serving, rabble-rousing narrative.
所以你们干嘛不让我们省省心
So why don't you do us all a favor
接受不可避免的现实呢
and just accept the inevitable?
你以为这是个笑话  你以为我在逗你玩
You think this is a joke? You think I'm playing with you?!
炸弹在哪里
Where's the bomb?!
-炸弹在哪里  -法伦  不要
- Where's the bomb?! - Fallon, no!
在哪里  目标是哪里  拉福德
Where is it? Where's the target, Radford?
-法伦  放下武器  -目标是哪里
- Lower your weapon, Fallon. - Where's the target?
法伦  马上放下武器
Fallon! Lower your weapon now!
除非他告诉我我问题的答案
Not until he tells me what I want to hear.
-在哪里  -放下武器
- Where is it?! - Lower your weapon!
你准备好上路了吗
You ready to go all the way? Huh?
我做好了为我的国家献身的准备
I'm prepared to die for my country.
你呢
Are you?
马上放下武器
Put down your weapon now.
嗨  我来吧
Hey. I got that.
谢谢
Thank you.
知道吗  他不会开口的
He wasn't gonna break, you know?
要是再多几天  或是一个周  还有可能
If I had a couple of days, maybe a week,
三个小时  不可能
but not in three hours.
我们得让他开口  我看到了突破口就利用了
We needed him to break. I saw an opening. I took it.
你侵犯了他的权利
You violated his rights.
我能想出一堆联邦律师
I can think of probably a dozen federal lawyers
他们都会不赞同你的说法
that would disagree with that.
他从未真正受到威胁
He was never in any real danger.
我把子弹从弹匣里取出了  枪压根没上膛
I removed the bullets from my clip. My gun wasn't even loaded.
-我的上了  -我知道
- Well, mine was. - Yeah. Well,
不过我很确定你不会开枪打我
I was pretty sure you weren't gonna shoot me.
要是有下一次  我可不会这么确定
You know, next time, I wouldn't be so sure.
探长  我明白你可能比较讨厌我
Detective, I understand that you probably hate me.
你俩都有这个权利
You have every right to, both of you.
但我的职责不是交朋友
But my job isn't to make friends.
而是阻止坏事发生
It's to stop bad things from happening.
还有几个小时我们就要眼睁睁看着
And seeing as how we're just a couple of hours
恐怖事件的发生
away from a major terrorist event
而现在我们竟一筹莫展
and we are basically back at square one.
我的确需要你的帮助
I could really use your help.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
老天  这家伙经过混蛋培训
Man, does that guy take Jackhole lessons
还是天生如此
or was he born that way?
都不是
Neither.
我问过我在国土安全局的朋友
I asked my buddy at D.H.S. about him.
原来他在911中失去了妻子
Turns out his wife was killed on 9/11.
她在第二座塔楼倒塌时丧命了
She rode the second tower down.
当时他们正在通话中
They were on the phone together when it happened.
他是对的
He's right.
要是不能撬开拉福德的嘴  我们就死定了
If we don't get Radford to talk, we're dead in the water.
也许不会
Maybe not.
我需要探测员前往
Okay, I need backpack detectors spread out
十个最可能被袭击的场所
to the ten most likely targets.
让核应急支援小组准备好  出发
Get the N.E.S.T. teams ready. Go.
杰马尔和阿米尔的同谋调查怎么样了
Where are we on Jamal and Amir's coconspirators?
共谋者
Coconspirators?
为什么  我们已经知道他们是替罪羊了
Why? We know that they're patsies.
记得拉福德说炸弹爆炸时的情况吗
Remember what Radford said about the bomb going off?
他说我们会找到恐怖分子
He said we will find our terrorist.
但杰马尔和阿米尔已经死了
But with Jamal and Amir out of the picture...
他们会想方设法嫁祸别人
They're gonna try to pin it on someone else.
跟他们俩都有关的某人
Somebody related to them both.
找出所有跟阿米尔和杰马尔·阿哈比
All right. Get locations on all known associates
有关系的人  不管之前
of Amir and Jamal Alhabi. I don't care
有没有排除他们
if we've dismissed 'em before.
不能漏过任何一个有中东血统的人
Anybody of middle-eastern origin or descent.
纳兹哈  阿米尔的妻子  找到她
Nazihah, Amir's wife, find her, track her down.
看她愿不愿意合作
See if she'll cooperate.
她信任你  也许她
She trusts you. Maybe she
-能帮我们缩小搜查范围  -现在就去
- can help us narrow down the list. - On it.
那是法伦派出的负责监视的人
That's Fallon's surveillance guy.
纳兹哈
Nazihah.
Nazihah!
纳兹哈
她不在  孩子也不在
She's gone. So is the kid.
什么
What?
我在桌子上发现了这个
I found this on the table.
"真主至大  上帝伟大  我执行光荣使命
"Allah Akbar. God is great. I go to my glory
处决那些无信仰者
against the forces of the infidel."
她是新的恐怖分子
She's their new terrorist.
他们会让她引爆炸弹
They're gonna have her set off the bomb.
-但谁都没看到劫持发生  -交通录像呢
- But none of them saw the abduction. - What about the traffic cams?
我派人去了  但还剩下不到两小时
I got teams out there, but with less than two hours left,
没有时间一个一个看了
There's no time to go through all the footage.
蒙哥马利哪去了
Where's Montgomery?
他在跟警局总部打电话协调
He's on the phone with one P.P. coordinating
城市急救队  以防万一
city emergency response teams, just in case.
依照完全辐射规程调动联邦应急事务管理局
Mobilize FEMA with full radiation protocol.
让他们协助空中补给  是的  长官
Have 'em standing by to airlift to the city. Yes, sir.
我们在她家中发现她的手机
We found her phone at the house.
-私家车停在前面  -就是说没法追踪她
- The family car is out in front. - So we have no way to trace her.
我有发现  根据国防部消息
Yo. I got something. According to D.O.D.,
跟拉福德在一个分队的人大多数还在部队里
most of the guys in Radford's unit are still deployed.
我找到了所有人  除了这两位
I was able to locate all but two--
伊凡·鲍尔和杰克·科克伦
Evan Bauer and Jack Cochran.
他们家人称上周起两人就去
Their families say they've been on a fishing trip
-钓鱼度假了  -他俩什么情况
- since last week. - What do we know about them?
鲍尔是武器专家
Well, Bauer is a weapons specialist,
科克伦则擅长爆炸品处理
and Cochran did a tour in explosive ordinance disposal.
国防部的人自然懂得如何组装炸弹
An D.O.D. guy would know how to build a bomb.
那好  马上组织人手
All right. Get a team together.
用显微镜给我查清这两个人的底细
Crawl up these guys' asses with a microscope.
电话记录  经济收支等等  找到他俩
Phone records, financials, anything--get a location.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我们找到这些人  你猜我们会看到什么
We find these guys, you know what we're gonna see?
什么都看不到
Nothing.
这些可不是还拿着学生签证的
These aren't brainwashed radicalized kids
被洗了脑的激进分子
on a student visa.
他们是受过严格训练的军人
This is highly trained military.
他们很可能早猜到我们的行动计划
They're probably reading out of our playbook.
我们没时间了
We are running out of time.
让核应急支援小组在空中待命
Get N.E.S.T. in the air.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
也许我们会有好运气
Maybe we'll get lucky,
地面行动小组能有所进展
The ground teams can make a move.
还有...
There, uh...
也许还有别的办法
There might be another way.
但...
But, uh...
我觉得你不会喜欢的
I don't think you're gonna like it.
打电话去
Make the call.
很简单  照我们说的做  每个人都能活
It's really very simple. Do what we ask, everybody lives.
不照我们说的做  每个人都得死
Don't do what we ask, everybody dies.
-就这么简单  -你杀了我丈夫
- It's as easy as that. - You killed my husband.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I believe you?
因为你别无选择
Because I'm afraid you have no other choice.
看见那辆面包车了吗
See the van?
你要做的就是驾驶它开到我们要求的地点
All you gotta do is drive it where we said,
停车  离开
park it, and walk away.
你照做  我们就把你的孩子还给你
You do that for us, we'll return your baby,
我们就可以继续彼此的生活
and we can all go on with our lives.
但是你要知道  驾驶座位旁有一个摄像机
But you should know, there's a camera on the driver's side.
如果你敢做什么蠢事  我们会知道的
If you do anything stupid, we'll know.
听明白了  就点点头
Nod if you understand.
卡塞尔先生
Mr. Castle.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
很高兴再次见到你们
So good to see you again.
法伦探员  久闻您的大名
And, Agent Fallon, your reputation precedes you.
叙利亚领事馆知道你在这儿吗
Does the Syrian consulate even know you're here?
上次我们见面的时候
When last we met,
贝克特探长  你拿走了我的手枪
Detective Beckett, you relieved me of my pistol.
我认为现在是把枪还给我的最好时机
I thought now was a good time to retrieve it.
尤瑟夫  上次我们见面的时候
Mr. Yusef, when we last met,
你告诉我保持消息灵通是你的工作
You told me it was in your business to stay informed.
就我的工作而言  我认为...
I find, in my business, it's important to...
知晓时事是很重要的
keep up with current events.
我肯定你的国家
And I'm sure that your country
会尽其全力
would do everything in its power
避免后果严重的误会的产生
to avoid a terrible misunderstanding.
如果因为未知原因阿米尔和他的妻子纳兹哈
If somehow Amir or his wife Nazihah
被错误地认为卷入了一场
were mistakenly believed to be involved
国内恐怖主义行动
in an act of domestic terrorism.
我得说  这是你我共同关心的事
I would say, it's in both our interests.
你也提到了阿米尔得到了你的特别关注
You also mentioned that Amir was of special interest to you.
我们叙利亚领事馆的人
We at the Syrian consulate
想要确认他喜欢自己的新家
wanted to make sure he liked his new home,
没错
So, yes.
我们时不时地会和他见面
we checked in with him from time to time.
那纳兹哈呢  你们会和她见面吗
And what about Nazihah, did you check in on her?
在这种情况下  我们认为去传达我们的悼念
Under the circumstances, we thought it would be appropriate
是合乎情理的事
to send our condolences.
你们监视她了  对吧
You had her under surveillance, didn't you?
她在哪
Where is she?
法伦先生  叙利亚领事馆
Mr. Fallon, the Syrian consulate
是一个严格遵守外交使命的机构
is strictly a diplomatic mission.
我们当然不会
We're certainly not
做出监视美国公民这种事
in the business of spying on U.S. citizens.
然而
However...
如果你们刚好去了第158街和富兰克林大街交口
if you were to happen by a red brick industrial building
的那栋红砖工厂厂房
on the corner of 158th street and Franklin,
我认为你们不会空手而归的
I do not think you'd be wasting your time.
现在请原谅  我要失陪了
Now if you'll excuse me,
我在城外有事情要办
I have an appointment outside the city.
是她的孩子
That's her baby.
孩子没事
The baby's fine.
纳兹哈在哪
Where's Nazihah?
伙计们  看那儿
Guys, over here.
摄像机角度太小  我们无法得知她在哪
Camera frame is too tight. We can't tell where she is.
没办法联系上她
No way to get in touch with her,
好让她知道她孩子安全了
and let her know her baby's all right.
我想我们得指望他了
Well, I guess it's all up to him.
他知道我们有截止时间  是吧
He knows we're on a deadline, right?
-他知道  -我是说字面意思
- Yeah, he knows. - I mean a literal deadline.
就是说如果过了时间  就死了
As in, you go over the line, you're dead.
卡塞尔  你就不能给他个机会吗
Castle, can you just give him a chance?
我愿意给他任何他想要的东西
I-I'm happy to give him anything he needs.
-是时间不等人  -通知所有小分队
- It's the clock that's not cooperating. - Alert all units.
目标开着一辆黑色面包车  重复  黑色面包车
Target is in a black van. Repeat, a black van.
她十分钟前去了时代广场
They left for Times Square ten minutes ago.
他们怎么开的口
How'd you get 'em to talk?
我骗了他们
I lied.
我说拉福德达成了协议  指控他俩
I told 'em Radford cut a deal implicating them both.
我要在时代广场设检查站和路障
I want checkpoints and barricades in Times Square.
让直升机在空中搜寻  找到那辆面包车
Get choppers in the air. Find that van.
她十分钟前离开的话
If she just left ten minutes ago,
我们有机会在她没抵达之前
There's a chance we can catch her
-找到她  -走百老汇大街或是河道街
- before she gets there. - Take Broadway or riverside.
我们走百老汇大街
We got Broadway.
你不应该走百老汇大街
You should not have taken Broadway.
那是去市中心最直接的路线
It's the most direct route to midtown.
是啊  但那不是最快的路线  我们应该...
Yeah, but it's not the fastest. We should cut over to--
卡塞尔  求你别指挥我开车行吗
Castle, will you please stop telling me how to drive?
我没有在指挥你...
I'm not telling you how to drive--
你就是在指挥我怎么开
You are telling me how to drive.
纳兹哈的丈夫是的哥
Nazihah's husband was a cabbie.
那又怎样
So?
百老汇大街在去市中心经过70几号街时交通堵塞
So Broadway slows down in the 70s through midtown.
她会知道最快的路线是走西区大街转11街
She would know that the fastest way is west end to 11th
然后在第48街穿城而过
and then cut crosstown on 48th.
为什么走第48街不走第46街
Okay, why 48th and not 46th?
因为第46街在施工  在这儿转弯
Because 46th has construction on it. Turn here.
所有分队注意  我是23号
All units, this is 23.
我们在百老汇大街跟踪一辆黑色面包车
We are tracking a black van southbound on Broadway
正经过第72街
passing 72nd.
重复  南向百老汇大街  经过第72街
I repeat, southbound on Broadway, passing 72nd.
-百老汇大街  -我...
- Broadway. - I, uh...
-我要掉头  -别  别
- I'm turning around. - No, no,
别掉头  那不是我们要找的面包车
don't turn around. It's the wrong van.
-卡塞尔  你怎么知道的  -在那儿
- Castle, how do you know? - There!
那儿  那儿  那儿  那儿
There! There! There! There! There! There!
是她
It's her.
靠边停车
Pull over!
纳兹哈  靠边停车
Nazihah, pull over!
求你们  别拦我  孩子在他们手上
Please, no. They have my baby.
纳兹哈  我们找到她了  她没事  她...
Nazihah, no. We've got her. She's okay. She's o--
总部  我是1L40
Dispatch, this is 1 Lincoln 40.
我们在第55街和第11街交口找到了炸弹
We found the bomb on 55th and 11th.
1L40  收到  拆弹部队在路上
1 Lincoln 40, copy. Bomb squad is en route.
预计到达时间三分钟
E.T.A. three minutes.
总部  炸弹还有一分多钟就爆炸了
Dispatch, that's about two minutes too late.
1L40  原地待命
1 Lincoln 40, stand by.
我是法伦
Fallon.
法伦  你知道怎么拆除炸弹吗
Fallon, you have any idea how to defuse a bomb?
-还有一分钟  -你在哪
- One minute. - Where are you?
-在第55街和第11街交口  -不行
- We're at 55th and 11th. - No,
我要看到炸弹才行  你能发张图片过来吗
I'd--I'd have to see it. Can you send a picture?
好的  等等
Yeah, yeah. Hold on.
在上传
It's uploading right now.
-45秒  -收到了吗
- 45 seconds. - You got it?
是的  在打开  缓冲中
Yeah, it's opening-- it's opening now.
-法伦  -等下
- Fallon? - Hang on!
-30秒  -法伦
- 30 seconds. - Fallon!
我什么都看不到
I can't see anything!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
卡塞尔
Castle...
Castle.
爽
Yes!
不  他  你们应该看看他当时的表情
No, he--no, you should've seen his face,
因为他停下
because he stopped,
看着我  然后他握住所有的线
he looked at me, he grabbed all the wires,
就这样拔了下来
and then he just yanked them.
所有的线吗
All of 'em?
我想其中肯定有对的那根
I figured one of 'em had to be the right one.
市长想给你们两个发勋章
You know, the mayor wants to give you guys a medal.
我没好意思提起
I didn't have the heart to tell him
-你根本就不知道自己在干什么  -谢谢
- you had no clue what you were doing. - Thank you.
队长说得对
The captain's right.
你们俩不知道你们有多幸运
You guys don't know how lucky you are.
事实上
Actually...
我知道
I do.
能跟你们两个谈谈吗
Could I talk to you two for a second?
我就是想让你们知道
I just want you two to know
美国地检官办公室会以多次实施
the U.S. Attorneys office is gonna be charging them
恐怖主义行动的罪名起诉他们
with multiple counts of conspiracy to commit terror.
多亏了你们两个  他们的罪名不需要加上
And thanks to you two, we won't have to add
谋杀广大无辜纽约市民了
the murder of innocent New Yorkers to that allegation.
我们不过是在做本职工作
Well, we were just doing our job.
实际上  我是在做本职工作  完全
Actually, I was doing my job. I don't know
-不知道他在干什么  -喂  但说得在理
- what the hell he was doing. - Hey. But that's true.
听着
Listen, um...
我所做的事情并不代表我就是那样的人
what I do is not who I am.
只是我不得不那样
It's just how I have to be.
希望你们两个能理解
I hope you both understand that.
这样说吧  我们很荣幸跟你合作
Why don't we just say it was a pleasure
同时希望再也不要跟你共事了
and that we hope that we don't have to do it again?
有道理
Fair enough.
不过如果这样的事又发生了
I-if it does happen again, though,
或许你可以给我发个短信  来个密语
maybe you could just text me, have a code word.
"跑"
"Run."
真是神奇的一天啊
Hell of a day, huh?
神奇的一天
Hell of a day.
你知道吗
You know...
我在想
I was thinking.
我在想也许
I was thinking maybe...
我该回家了
I should go home,
休息一下
get some rest.
累死了
Long day.
晚安
Good night.